
<!-- <?xml version='1.0'?> -->

<!--

IF YOU CAN READ THIS, YOUR BROWSER DOESN'T SUPPORT XML.

PLEASE UPDATE YOUR BROWSER, OR VIEW THE HTML VERSION OF THIS PAGE.

-->
<!--
When the schema works, reference it like this; change the project tag below to this
<project xmlns:xsi = "http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation = "isd-personnel.xsd">
-->
<project>
  <name>Kasper</name>
  <title>Knowledge Acquisition for Solving Problems</title>
  <description>
    <short>
    DARPA's Rapid Knowledge Formation (RKF) goal is to enable distributed teams of subject matter
    experts (SMEs) to enter and modify knowledge directly and easily, without the need for
    specialized training in knowledge representation, acquisition, or manipulation. 
    </short>
    <long>
    <n/> is an integration effort with other research groups to develop
    tools to enable domain experts to extend knowledge bases by using natural
    language interfaces, commonsense reasoning, and analogy-based reasoning. Our
    group's contributions focus on tools to formulate follow-up questions when
    users have not provided sufficient knowledge, and on the acquisition of
    problem solving and process knowledge. The integrated system will be tested by
    two challenge problems designed by DARPA. One problem is based on how our
    system will acquire graduate level knowledge of biology from a textbook and
    then answer the questions at the end of the chapter. Another challenge problem
    will require developing expert-level knowledge-based techniques for advanced
    genome annotation and exploitation for pathogen countermeasures. 
    </long>
  </description>
  <research>
    <short>
   Knowledge acquisition with natural language.
    </short>
    <long>
    We are interested in developing tools that enable users to specify new knowledge in natural language,
    so that they are more accessible to end users. We have developed an interface that allows users to
    modify methods by manipulating their paraphrase in English. It allows the user to select a portion
    of the paraphrase that corresponds to a valid expression and picking from a menu of suggestions for
    other expressions that can be used to replace it. Generating sensible suggestions is one of the
    challenging aspects of this work.
    </long>
  </research>
  <funding>
    <program>DARPA Rapid Knowledge Formation (RKF)</program>
    <url>http://reliant.teknowledge.com/RKF/</url>
    <awardnumber>(none)</awardnumber>
    <startdate>April 2000</startdate>
    <enddate>November 2002</enddate>
  </funding>
  <link>DARPA <a href='http://reliant.teknowledge.com/RKF/'>Rapid Knowledge Formation (RKF) program</a></link>
</project>
