
<!-- <?xml version='1.0'?> -->

<!--

IF YOU CAN READ THIS, YOUR BROWSER DOESN'T SUPPORT XML.

PLEASE UPDATE YOUR BROWSER, OR VIEW THE HTML VERSION OF THIS PAGE.

-->
<!-- 
When the schema works, reference it like this; change the project tag below to this 
<project xmlns:xsi = "http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation = "isd-personnel.xsd">
-->
<project>
  <name>Temple</name>
  <title>Template Enhancement through Knowledge Acquisition</title>
  <description>
    <short>
    <n/> is an acquisition interface for planning knowledge that relies on script-based wizards
    to guide users in adding planning constraints and preferences.
    </short>
    <long>
    The Active Templates program (AcT) will produce a robust, lightweight software technology for aiding in the automation of
    detailed planning and execution for military operations and other highly-coordinated activities using a plan spreadsheet
    metaphor. Active Templates are distributed data structures whose variables will be linked to live data feeds or
    problem-solving methods. Active Templates will assist with automated planning and execution by capturing, improving and
    updating critical information such as current state, goals, constraints, alternative actions, standard defaults,
    problem-solving context over time, decisions, and rationale. Active Templates will be designed to be user-tailorable,
    networked, noise-tolerant, user-supported, scalable and widely adopted. 
    <P/>Within AcT, the <n/> project is developing software tools to aid a user in adding new
    constraints to active templates. This work makes use of prior work on problem-solving
    methods and script-based acquisition for plan evaluation
    performed under HPKB and ARPI.
    </long>
  </description>
  <research>
    <short>
    Ontologies and background knowledge, knowledge aquisition scripts, dependency analysis.
    </short>
    <long>
    <ul>
    <li>Ontologies and background knowledge</li>
    <li>Knowledge aquisition scripts</li>
    <li>Dependency analysis</li>
    </ul>
    </long>
  </research>
  <funding>
    <program>DARPA Active Templates (AcT)</program>
    <url>http://schafercorp-ballston.com/active-templates</url>
    <awardnumber>F30602-00-2-0513</awardnumber>
    <startdate>April 2000</startdate>
   <enddate>July 2003</enddate>
  </funding>
  <link><a href='http://schafercorp-ballston.com/active-templates'>DARPA Active Templates (AcT) program</a></link>
</project>
