<!-- <?xml version='1.0'?> -->

<!--

IF YOU CAN READ THIS, YOUR BROWSER DOESN'T SUPPORT XML.

PLEASE UPDATE YOUR BROWSER, OR VIEW THE HTML VERSION OF THIS PAGE.

-->
<!--
When the schema works, reference it like this; change the project tag below to this
<project xmlns:xsi = "http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation = "isd-personnel.xsd">
-->
<project>
  <name>TRELLIS</name>
  <title>Capturing and Exploiting Semantic Relationships for Information and Knowledge Management</title>

  <status>
<b><n /></b> provides an interactive environment that allows users to add their observations, opinions, and conclusions as they analyze information by making semantic annotations to documents and other on-line resources. Our work to date has concentrated on three major areas: 1) designing a vocabulary to annotate information analysis, 2) creating semantic markup representations for this vocabulary and annotating analysis products, and 3) developing an initial prototype of the <n /> interface and tools.
<p />
We have released in August 2001 our first version of <n />.  <n /> includes a vocabulary for semantic annotations of decisions and tradeoffs.  The initial version of this vocabulary is now available as a schema/ontology in XMLS, RDFS, and DAML+OIL. <n /> allows users to extend this vocabulary and its corresponding schemas.  For each analysis performed by a user with <n />, the system generates annotations in XML, RDF, and DAML+OIL according to the schemas and ontologies for the <n /> annotation vocabulary.  Users can extend the vocabulary using the <n /> interface, adding perhaps domain specific terms or constructs that are useful to their particular task.
<p />
We have exercised <n /> to date with a variety of scenarios to annotate tradeoffs and decisions (e.g., travel), organizing materials (e.g., search results), analyzing disagreements and controversies on a topic (e.g., political debates), and handling incomplete information (e.g., genealogy research).
<br />
  </status>

  <description>
    <short>
<n/> is an interactive environment that allows users to add their observations, viewpoints, and conclusions as they  analyze information by making semantic annotations to documents and other on-line resources. We view this as a knowledge acquisition problem, where users are adding new knowledge to the system based on their expertise as they analyze information.
    </short>

    <long>
<n/> is an interactive environment that allows users to add their observations, viewpoints, and conclusions as they  analyze information by making semantic annotations to documents and other on-line resources. We view this as a knowledge acquisition problem, where users are adding new knowledge to the system based on their expertise as they analyze information.
     <p>The key innovative ideas behind our approach are:</p>
     <ul>
     <li>
     Supporting users to create knowledge fragments from the original sources
     as well as from other fragments. The key is to capture how a developer
     progressively generates new knowledge that results in added value to the
     original raw information sources. Our goal is to support users to
     highlight key salient information from large reports and documents, to
     add new knowledge fragments based on their analysis and integration of
     existing information, and to finally create semi-formal fragments.</li>
     </ul>

     <ul>
     <li>
     Capturing and exploiting semantic interrelationships among information
     items. <n/> will 1) facilitate semantic markup of relationships
     between different pieces of knowledge, 2) exploit semantic markups
     in given problem solving contexts, and 3) suggest additional relationships
     based on those already specified by the user. Users will be encouraged
     and rewarded to add valuable annotations over raw information sources,
     since the more annotations they add the more help the system can provide
     in their work. When the user chooses to do little or no annotation,
     the system will provide weaker support (based on default heuristics and
     strategies) and will still help the user as much as possible.</li>
     </ul>

     <ul>
     <li>
     Extensible semantic markup of information items and their relationships.
     Users will be able to draw from a core semantic markup language that will
     contain a basic domain-independent vocabulary to formulate annotations.
     They will also be able to extend this core language with additional terminology
     useful in their particular domain. Using this language, users will
     be able to annotate not only the information items themselves, but they
     will also be able to annotate the relationships among them, which will
     enable them to qualify and describe interdependencies between different
     information sources and how they relate to a new conclusion or assessment
     added by the developer. In essence, links between the information
     items will be first class citizens in the knowledge base.</li>
     </ul>

     <p>Below is a diagram of the current <n/> architecture. A
     User typically starts searching the Web for a certain document, or indicating
     a pointer to a specific Web resource that contains useful information.
     Each is considered an information item. Information items may include
     raw information sources (an image, a text document, a video, etc.) as well
     as products of previous analysis (by the user or by other users.)
     All the information items are in some sense the knowledge base that <n/>
     operates on, and we refer to it as the Semantically Marked Information
     Base, or SMIB. We refer to an information item as an EI2 (Extended
     Information Items).</p>

     <center>
	  <img src="arch.jpg"/>
	  </center>

     <p>Users extend the SMIB using two tools: the Annotation Tool and the Creation
     Tool. They can use the EI2 Annotation Tool to add semantic annotations
     to an EI2 to describe its contents and to relate them to other EI2.
     For example, an EI2 may be annotated as containing a map, or an interesting
     event. The Annotation tool can also be used to relate EI2.
     The tool will provide an editor with a set of connectors. An example
     is a connector to denote that two EI2s are contradictory. This way,
     the user may link an EI2 that contains a description of a product as having
     a tag price of $20 to another EI2 that has the same product with
     a price of $25.</p>
     <p>The Annotation tool draws on a library of semantic annotations and connectors
     that will be based on a core domain-independent language defined by the
     Semantic Annotation Vocabulary. An Interdependency Schema defines
     a vocabulary for connectors based on a variety of dimensions: pertinence,
     reliability, credibility, structural (x is example of y, x is part of y,
     x describes y, etc.) causality (x1 x2...xn contribute to y, x1 x2...xn
     indicate y, etc.) temporal ordering (x before y, x after y, x simultaneous
     with y, etc.), argumentation (x may be reason for y, x supports y, etc.).
     The Domain Schema contains a core vocabulary to annotate the content of
     documents that extends the Interdependency Schema with domain terms.
     Our plan is that <n/> will provide a core vocabulary, and users will
     be able to extend it with additional terms.</p>
     <p>The Creation Tool enables users to create new EI2. For example,
     a user may create an EI2 as an assessment that he or she formulates based
     on existing EI2. If a combination of some subparts of EI2 lets a
     user conclude or decide on some definition, then the subparts can be captured
     into a new Information Item, that drops all other irrelevant parts of the
     original EI2. A new EI2 can be added by extracting or summarizing
     some of the previous results.</p>
     <p>Below is a snapshot of the current user interface of <n/>.
     In this case, a user is using <n/> to decide whether a mission to take
     Navy SEALs to Athens is feasible. Given the Web sources consulted
     and the indicated capabilities of the SEAL team (shown on the left), the
     user has entered the rationale for deciding that the operation is not feasible.</p>

     <center>
	  <img src="snapshot.jpg"/>
	  </center>

     <p/><p>We plan to extend <n/> with learning and adaptive techniques
     in order to offer to the user improved and extended capabilities over time.
     As users annotate more EI2 and create new EI2 that capture their analysis,
     <n/> will be able to exploit this information and become increasingly
     more proactive. We also plan to add a Query Facility that will allow
     users to search the SMIB based on the semantic annotations of the EI2.
     It will include a structured editor to guide users to formulate queries
     using the semantic annotation vocabulary defined in the schemas.</p>
     <p>In summary, <n/> provides users with tools that enable them to specify
     information in increasingly more structured form, and to specify semantic
     annotations that can be exploited for processing and integration of separate
     information items.</p><br/>
    </long>
  </description>

  <research>
    <short>
    Semantic Markup, Rationale Capture, Knowledge Aquisition.
    </short>
    <long>
	 <p />
	 <ul>
<li>Developing a vocabulary to support semantic annotations for information interdependencies to capture the rationale for decisions as well as traces to the original information sources used. Our initial version of this language draws from research in various areas, including argumentation and discourse relations, logic deduction, process and plan representations, and event understanding.<br /></li> 

<li>Developing semantic annotations of decisions and tradeoffs through the use of markup languages.  The initial version of this vocabulary is now available as a schema/ontology in <a href="http://www.w3.org/XML/Schema">XMLS</a>, <a href="http://www.w3.org/TR/rdf-schema/">RDFS</a>, and <a href="http://www.daml.org">DAML+OIL</a>. TRELLIS allows users to extend this vocabulary and its corresponding schemas.
A nice result of this work is a <a href="http://trellis.semanticweb.org/comparison.html">comparison table</a> of semantic markup languages that helped us the features and tradeoffs of existing markup languages.  This table compares the features of XML Schema, RDF Schema, and DAML+OIL and is linked to examples of use of each feature. We also have tutorial <a href="http://trellis.semanticweb.org">slides</a> on semantic markup languages that highlight their features.<br /></li>

<li>Developing an <a href="http://excalibur.isi.edu:8888/trellis_web/">interface</a> that helps users annotate information analysis and decision rationale.  The first version of this interface was released in August 2000 and includes a creation tool, an annotation tool, and search and collaborative capabilities.  We have used it to developed several scenarios that demonstrate generality of the approach, including intelligence analysis, genealogy research, and travel planning.<br /></li>

<li>Annotating the design rationale of knowledge bases, to create a new generation of "Resilient Hyper Knowledge Bases" (RHKBs) that contain pointers to the original sources of knowledge as well as the analysis and decisions of the knowledge engineers that built it.<br /></li>
    </ul>
    </long>
  </research>

  <link>
  <b>The Semantic Web</b>
  <ul>
  <li><a href="http://www.w3c.org/">World Wide Web consortium</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.w3c.org/DesignIssues/Semantic.html">Tim Berners-Lee's vision of the Sematic Web</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.w3c.org/DesignIssues/Semantic.html">The Semantic Web</a> and its
    <a href="http://www.semanticweb.org/">Organization</a></li>
  </ul>
  </link>

  <link>
  <b>Markup Languages &amp; Tools</b>
  <ul>
  <li><a href="http://www.w3.org/RDF/">RDF</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.w3.org/XML/">XML</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.daml.org/">DAML</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://dtsn.darpa.mil/iso/programtemp.asp?mode=347">The DARPA Agent Markup Language (DAML) program</a>
    and its <a href="http://www.daml.org/">extended community</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  </link>

  <link>
  <b>Related Projects</b>
  <ul>
  <li><a href="http://www.cs.umd.edu/projects/plus/SHOE/">SHOE</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://ontobroker.aifb.uni-karlsruhe.de/">OntoBroker</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.dublincore.org/">The Dublic Core Metadata Initiative</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.w3.org/Metadata/Activity.html">W3C Metadata working group</a></li>
  </ul>
  </link>

<!-- Demo -->
<demo>
<center>
<b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="+1">A Screen Walkthrough
Demonstration of <n /></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica">Version 1.0, August 2001</font></b></center>

<p /><b><i><font face="Arial,Helvetica">Brief Overview</font></i></b>
<p /><n /> is an interactive environment that will allow users to add their
observations, viewpoints, and conclusions as they analyze information by
making semantic annotations to documents and other on-line resources. We
view this as a knowledge acquisition problem, where users are adding new
knowledge to the system based on their expertise as they analyze information.
<p /><n /> can be accessed from the main project page at <a href="http://trellis.semanticweb.org">http://trellis.semanticweb.org</a>,
or from <a href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/trellis">http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/trellis</a>.
<p />Each analysis that the user performs has a purpose that is used to describe
the issue analyzed. <n /> asks the user to specify a purpose, which
is a short sentence that summarizes the issue or hypothesis in question.
<p />Each piece of information or data that is used in the analysis is called
a statement. A statement can be linked to a Web resource, it could
be a manual or authoritative source. <n /> allows the user to access
a Web search engine and use the results of the search to create new statements.
Users can also enter statements that are not Web pages but instead have
text such as an email message, or a note about a conversation, or any other
text. The user can specify a URL but it is not necessary. In
addition to input information and data, the user can add statements that
indicate intermediate conclusions or hypothesis. Statements can also
be used to indicate the sources of some information. Sources can
be qualified according to the user's view on their reliability and credibility.
The user can define new statements or modify existing ones at any time.
<p />The overall analysis is composed of units, which are composed in turn
of sub-units. Each unit relates individual statements using a construct
from the <n /> vocabulary. All the statements within a unit are linked
to some Web source or user-provided text. Users can provide reasons
("because…") or not, depending on the amount of detail that they wish to
capture in each part of the analysis. Only some portions of a given
unit are part of the <n /> language. The rest of the components
of the unit (i.e., the statements) are treated as strings and <n /> will
not process them further.
At any time, users can compose their analysis from the statements that
they have selected and created. The analysis of a purpose is made
of units, which may have sub-units in turn. Users can collapse or
expand any portions of the analysis and manipulate units and sub-units
to refine their interdependencies. Users can also rearrange the units in
the analysis by dragging and dropping them in the analysis window.
This is useful in cases where the analysis is done bottom-up and the users
wants to relate units that were created previously separately.
<p />Sometimes a user does not know yet how to use a statement in an analysis
but would like to have that statement included in the analysis frame.
Users can select statements and include them in the analysis under a 'Notes
and other information' category. This facility is also useful to
drag and drop statements into the analysis.
<p />Users can also import statements and units from other users if they
are relevant to your purpose. The user can do keyword search in either
purpose names or statement titles entered by other users.
<p /><n /> can be used offline if you cache Web pages before disconnecting
from the network. Statements can be selected and a cached copy of their
corresponding Web pages is created and used until otherwise indicated.
<p />Users can view the results of their analysis annotated in several markup
languages: XML, RDF, and DAML, corresponding to the Schemas and ontologies
that define the <n /> vocabulary.
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><i><font face="Arial,Helvetica">Screen Walkthrough of an Example</font></i></b>
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">Start with the Login Screen.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageRD5.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">Each analysis that the
user performs has a "purpose" that is used to describe the issue analyzed.<br />
After logging in, you are presented with the purposes which you have (or
a person with your login ID has) made so far. By default, there are 3 purposes
which are added for each new user.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageRP6.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">You can make a new purpose
by the "New Purpose" button, which prompts for the name of the new purpose</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageQJJ.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">After creating a new purpose
OR when editing an existing purpose, you end up with the <i><u>purpose
editor window </u></i>as shown below. The left side of the screen is used
to find, select, and edit the statements used in analyzing the purpose.<br />
The right side of the screen is used to construct and view the details
of the analysis.</font></b><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">A <i><u>query frame</u></i>
is in the top left hand side, in which you can fire off queries to a search
engine (in this version of <n /> the search engine is Google), and get
the results in the <i><u>results frame</u></i> below.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">There is nothing in the
current selections here, since this is a new purpose. Nor is there anything
in the <i><u>statements frame</u></i>, which is the frame shown in the
lower left of the screen</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/image7GI.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">The results from the search
engine that you find relevant can be selected by clicking their icon and
clicking on 'Add Selections'.<br /> The Web pages selected are added to
the statements frame at the bottom left.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br />
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageCPO.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">The selected pages can
be renamed to reflect the salient fact that they contain that needs to
be brought up in the analysis of the overall purpose.<br /> You can rename
something by selecting it and pressing Ren (one of the buttons for editing
of current selections).<br /> A selected page can also be deleted (selecting
it and then clicking on the Delete button).<br /> Anything in the statements
frame can also be moved to the analysis frame on the right hand side to
start building the analysis (by selecting it and clicking the "Move ->"
button).</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageGEQ.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">Not all statements come
from Web pages.<br /> You can also add new statements manually, for example
an email message, or a note about a conversation, or any other text.<br />
This is done by clicking on "Add user data".<br /> You can specify a URL
if you wish, but it is not necessary.</font></b><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">Any new statements entered
manually also have to be selected in order to be added to the statements
frame and ultimately to the analysis.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br />
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageTGQ.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">Some statements denote
a source (e.g., CNN) that you want to cite in your analysis.<br /> You
can describe a source in detail using the 'Desc' button as shown. This
description will be shown whenever you click on this source statement.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageF1O.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">You can also view user-entered
statements by clicking on them.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/image3MG.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">To modify a user-entered
statement, select it and click on the Edit button, then enter the new information.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageFTV.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">At any time, you can compose
your analysis from the statements that you have selected and created.<br />
The analysis of a purpose is made of units, which may have sub-units in
turn.<br /> Click the "Add Unit" button, where you can select statements
and constructs from the <n /> language in order to create an expression.<br />
You can also annotate the source of the analysis and qualify the source
for its reliability and credibility.</font></b><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">You can build a unit using
the default <n /> constructs, but you can also define your own by selecting
"New".</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br />
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageQLE.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">Units are normally shown
as a collapsible list that the user can select and expand. If any sub-units
are added after selecting a statement, they will be added under this statement
in the collapsible tree.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageOEU.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">You can also use statements
and units from other users if they are relevant to your purpose.<br />
To do this, click on the "Import" button and you will be prompted for a
keyword to search (here 'Iraq') in either Purpose names or Statement titles
entered by other users.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageKD4.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">From the results obtained,
you can select a purpose.<br /> The system will show an uneditable version
of the analysis frame. You can select any unit and import it.<br /> Notice
that if you select the top unit the entire analysis is imported.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageVV3.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">After importing, the selected
units and sub-units (along with the statements used in them) as well as
the sources are added to your own set.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/image270.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">You can also rearrange
the units in the analysis by dragging and dropping them in the analysis
frame.<br /> This is useful if you do your analysis bottom-up and want
to relate units that you created previously separately.</font></b><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">To move a unit, select
it first by moving the mouse to the left side of the triangle widget and
clicking on it.<br /> Hold down the mouse and move it to the place
where you want the unit to be.<br /> A black line shows the position where
the unit would be dropped.<br /> A transparent box shows its future parent
unit. (So you can either drag to, or into).</font></b><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">There are 2 modes of dragging
: Left-click and drag drags the whole tree (as shown), and right click
and drag just drags the particular unit.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br />
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageCE4.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">After the unit has been
moved:</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageF1H.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"><n /> can be used offline
if you cache Web pages before disconnecting from the network. Select a
statement and click 'Toggle'. This link now points to a cached copy. A
link pointing to a cached copy is highlighted in a darker green color.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageTQT.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">Sometimes you do not know
yet how you want to use a statement in an analysis but you want to include
it in the analysis frame. You can select statements and move them to the
analysis frame with the 'Move->' button. These selections go under a 'Notes
and other information' category.</font></b><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">This facility is useful
to drag and drop statements into the analysis.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br />
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageTLJ.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">You can modify units in
the analysis frame by clicking on the "Edit" button.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">The "Remove" button deletes
the selected unit and all of its sub-units.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">The "Restore" button is
used as a single-step undo.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">The "Extract" button is
used after selecting a statement. Then all the sources that it finds inside
the statement are added to the current selections.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">You can also view the
results of your analysis annotated in several markup languages. To view
this, go back to the Main Screen where you can see the marked up versions
of the purposes that were just edited, by clicking on the 'XML' button
for the XML markup, 'RDF' button for RDF markup and 'DAML' button for the
DAML version.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">In this example, the XML
version of the 'Use of chemical weapons by Iraq' purpose is shown:</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br />
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageLS3.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">You can also see the Schemas
(DTD, XML Schema) for the XML data, the RDF Schema for the RDF data, and
the DAML ontology by clicking the respective buttons on top of the screen.</font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageRP7.JPG" />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">The 'Save' Button is used
to take a single backup of all your purposes. If at a later time, the 'Restore'
button is clicked, all the purposes from the time that 'Save' was clicked
are restored.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">The 'Help' Button brings
up a User Guide.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1">The 'Logout' Button brings
you back to the Login page.</font></b>
<br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b><br /><b><font face="Arial,Helvetica" size="-1"></font></b>
<p /><img src="demoimages/imageRP6.JPG" />
</demo>
</project>
