<!-- <?xml version='1.0'?> -->

<!--

IF YOU CAN READ THIS, YOUR BROWSER DOESN'T SUPPORT XML.

PLEASE UPDATE YOUR BROWSER, OR VIEW THE HTML VERSION OF THIS PAGE.

-->
<!--
When the schema works, reference it like this; change the project tag below to this
<project xmlns:xsi = "http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation = "isd-personnel.xsd">
-->
<project>
  <name>KANAL</name>
  <title>Knowledge Analysis on Process Models"</title>

  <status>
    <short>
  Our initial evaluation of <n /> as a stand-alone system shows its usefulness
in finding errors and suggesting fixes.  It also has been
successfully integrated within an end-to-end system that support users
entering domain knowledge as a part of DARPA Rapid Knowledge Formation (RKF)
program. 
  </short>
  <long>
<b><n /></b> is a tool for building and checking process models.  By
relating different pieces of information in process models among themselves
and to the existing KB, it performs a variety of verification and validation
checks and propose useful fixes.
  <p />

We performed an initial evaluation in December 2000, which has been reported in
<a 
href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/rkf/KANAL/kanal-ijcai01.pdf">Kim and
Gil, IJCAI-01</a>.  The results show that <n /> can find most of the errors in
the process models and suggest useful fixes including the fixes that directly
point to the sources of the errors.
<p />

<n /> has been successfully integrated within an end-to-end system (called
SHAKEN) that supports subject matter experts entering domain knowledge as part
of the DARPA <a href="http://reliant.teknowledge.com/RKF/">Rapid Knowledge
Formation (RKF)</a> program.  During summer 2001, the SHAKEN system has been
evaluated by lightly trained biologists where they author biology textbook
knowledge using the system.  The resulting knowledge bases 
answer questions that a student might be asked based on the
chapter's contents.
</long>
 
  </status>

  <description>
    <short>
     <n/> is a tool for building and checking process models.  By
relating different pieces of information in process models among themselves
and to the existing KB, it performs a variety of verification and validation
checks and propose useful fixes.
    </short>

    <long>
<p />
Helping end users build and check process models is a challenge for many
science and engineering fields.  Many AI researchers have investigated useful
ways of verifying and validating knowledge bases for ontologies and rules, but
it is not easy to directly apply them to checking process models.  Other
techniques developed for checking and refining planning knowledge tend to
focus on automated plan generation rather than helping users author process
information.  In this paper, we propose a complementary approach which helps
users author and check process models.  Our system, called <a
href="KANAL-description.txt"><n /></a>(Knowledge 
ANALysis), relates pieces of information in process models among themselves
and to the existing KB, analyzing how different pieces of input are put
together to achieve some effect.  It builds interdependency models from this
analysis and uses them to find errors and propose fixes.  
(<a
href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/rkf/KANAL/kanal-ijcai01.pdf">Kim and Gil, IJCAI-01</a>)

<p />
<n /> builds upon previous work on <a
href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/">EXPECT</a> using Interdependency Models (<a
href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/link/publications.html#Kim-Gil-AAAI-99">Kim and Gil
AAAI-99</a>, <a
href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/link/publications.html#Kim-Gil-AAAI-2000">Kim and Gil
AAAI-2000</a>).  The work on EXPECT analyzed problem-solving interdependencies,
which model how different pieces of problem solving (procedural) knowledge
relate to each other and to the class definitions in domain ontologies.  Our
initial work concentrates on <i>process models</i>, i.e., knowledge
describing activities and subprocesses as well as their relationships.

<p />
Currently, <n />'s checks are done on the simulated execution of the process
model.  Using skolem instances, we can check general scenarios of the
animation of a process. The result of each animation are used as a model of
interdependencies among the sub-steps of the process model.  <n /> performs a
variety of verification checks to process models, including <i>unachieved
conditions of steps</i> in a process model, <i>expected and unexpected
effects, potential loops</i>, and <i>disjunctive model branches</i>.  <n />
will also help users with validation checks of <i> redundancies</i>, and
<i>resource use</i> within a process model.


    </long>
  </description>

  <research>
    <short>
     Process Models, Verification and Validation, Knowledge Acquisition
    </short>
    <long>
<n /> checks process models specified by a user reports possible errors in
the models, and generates specific suggestions to the user about how to fix
those errors.  Our approach is inspired on previous work on <a
href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/">EXPECT</a> using Interdependency Models (<a
href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/link/publications.html#Kim-Gil-AAAI-99">Kim and Gil
AAAI-99</a>, <a
href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/link/publications.html#Kim-Gil-AAAI-2000">Kim and Gil
AAAI-2000</a>).  KANAL analyzes the interdependencies among the individual
steps of a process model.  For example, a simulation of the execution of the
steps allows KANAL to anlayze interdependencies between the conditions and
effects of different steps, such as that the required conditions for each step
are met when the step is supposed to take place, and that the expected effects
of the overall process are in fact obtained.

<p /> The kinds of checks performed and the kinds of fixes proposed by <n /> include

<ul>
<li> Unachieved Preconditions
</li>
<li> Unachieved Expected Effects
</li>
<li> Unordered Steps
</li>
<li> Inappropriate Execution of Steps
</li>
<li> Inappropriate Loops
</li>
<li> Inappropriate Disjunctive Branches
</li>
<li> Inappropriate Branches
</li>

</ul>

    </long>
  </research>

  <link>
   <a href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/KANAL/api.txt">KANAL API</a>
  </link>
  <link>
   <a href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/KANAL/releases.html">KANAL Implementation on KM</a>
  </link>

  <link>
  KANAL slides in various meetings 
  <ul>
  <li><a href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/KANAL/slides/KANAL-SRI-meeting-10-00.ppt">SRI RKF meeting (10/11/00)</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/KANAL/slides/KANAL-jan-01-rkf.ppt">RKF PI meeting (Jan/01)</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/KANAL/slides/test-k-intro-in-training.ppt">Test Knowledge (intro)
(April)</a></li>
  <li><a href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/KANAL/slides/Virus-Invades-Cell-trial-in-shaken.ppt"> design of the KANAL
interface (a) (Mar/01)</a></li> 
  <li><a href="http://www.isi.edu/expect/projects/KANAL/slides/Virus-Invades-Cell-in-shaken.ppt"> design of the KANAL
interface (b) (Mar/01)</a></li>
  </ul>
  </link>



<!-- Demo -->
<demo>
<P>

</P>



     <center>
	  <img src="../tn_comingsoon.jpg"/>
	  </center>


</demo>
</project>
